Contact

cgoetten@live.com

www.linkedin.com/in/coribrown-8436968a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Facilities Management

Nursing

Time Management

Certifications

Advanced Practice Registered Nurse (APRN) Verification for DEA Number

Water Safety Instructor

BLS Instructor

Honors-Awards

March of Dimes Nurse of the Year: General Medicine

Campus Recreation Executive Director Award

Cori Brown

Family Nurse Practitioner at Fast Pace Health

Greater Nashville Area, TN

Summary

Experienced Travel Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Microsoft Word, Facility Management (FM), Vital Signs, Management, and Healthcare. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science (B.S.) focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Illinois State University.

Experience

Fast Pace Health
Family Nurse Practitioner
March 2020 - Present (4 months)
Dickson, Tennessee, United States

South College
Adjunct Nursing Faculty
August 2018 - Present (1 year 11 months)
Greater Nashville Area, TN

Teach undergraduate nursing students in clinical and simulation settings and explain skills they will be performing within their own nursing practice

TriStar Centennial Medical Center Nurse Leader May 2016 - January 2019 (2 years 9 months) Greater Nashville Area, TN

Orthopedics/Total Joint Replacement | Bone Marrow Transplant

Vanderbilt University Medical Center Staff RN - PRN 2016 - September 2017 (1 year) Breast Center & Medical Infusion Clinic

Outpatient Medical Infusion & Breast Cancer chemotherapy

Onward Healthcare

Travel RN

August 2016 - May 2017 (10 months)

Nasvhille, TN

Travel Assignment: Centennial Medical Center - Nashville, TN

- Facility type: Acute Care Hospital

- Total beds: 657

- Unit: Orthopedics/Total Joint Replacement

- Unit beds: 29

- Caseload: 4-5 patients

American Traveler Staffing Professionals Travel RN

October 2015 - July 2016 (10 months)

Denver, CO

Travel Assignment: Rose Medical Center - Denver, CO

- Facility type: Acute Care Hospital

Total beds: 350Unit: SurgicalUnit beds: 24

- Caseload: 4-6 patients

Barnes-Jewish Hospital RN BSN

July 2014 - September 2015 (1 year 3 months)

St. Louis

Division 6900 Bone Marrow Transplant - Leukemia, Lymphoma, Myeloma

- Responsible for 3-4 high acuity patient assignments in a complex environment involving many clinical trials
- Collaborate with a multidisciplinary team working closely with physicians, nurses, patient care technicians, and therapists to formulate, implement and modify patient care
- Educate patients and their families on the importance of infection prevention, medication compliance, nutrition, and activity
- Utilize critical thinking while monitoring lab results, intake and output, vital signs, wounds, and level of consciousness and report any abnormal findings to physician
- Completed Nurse Residency Program and Oncology Specialty Orientation Program
- Chair of Barnes-Jewish Hospital Division 6900 Unit Practice Council
- Member of Barnes-Jewish Hospital Clinical Practice Council

Jerseyville Parks & Recreation Manager/Water Safety Instructor May 2008 - May 2015 (7 years 1 month)

- Supervised approximately 32 employees and ensured they were performing tasks appropriately
- Accountable for cash handling and depositing cash from daily admissions and concessions
- Ensured a safe swimming environment for all patrons and guests
- Prepared and instructed lessons based on the American Red Cross swim curriculum and evaluated students' swim progress
- Placed food orders and took inventory on all products
- · Submitted work orders for maintenance issues and followed up on progress
- · Scheduled all 32 employees within the facility

Illinois State University Campus Recreation Facility Manager October 2009 - May 2014 (4 years 8 months)

- Supervise approximately 12 employees at a time and all guests in the building
- · Responsible for reconciliation and daily cash handling
- Ensure a safe and clean environment for all patrons in a 170,000 square foot building
- Handle all emergency and non-emergency situations within the building while on shift

Jersey Community Hospital Wellness Center Front Desk Employee, Water Safety Instructor, Lifeguard, Day-Care Employee August 2008 - 2014 (6 years)

August 2000 - 2014 (0 years

Jerseyville, IL

- Promoted and encouraged various wellness programs and classes
- Responsible for cash handling from membership dues, programs, JCH
 Wellness gear, concessions, and The Lean Bean (coffee shop)
- Provided childcare and babysitting services
- Maintained a safe swimming environment for all members and guests
- Taught swimming lessons based on the American Red Cross swim curriculum and evaluated students' swim progress

Heartland Health Certified Nursing Assistant July 2011 - April 2012 (10 months)

- Assist residents in all aspects of daily living including, personal hygiene, toileting, feeding, ambulating, and turning bedridden residents
- Monitor resident's behavior and physical condition for progress or deterioration, by taking vital signs
- Execute a clean, organized and tidy facility, by bed making and light housekeeping
- Chart accurately on each resident daily and report off to the next shift

Education

Maryville University of Saint Louis

Master of Science - MS, Family Practice Nurse/Nursing · (2017 - 2019)

Illinois State University

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2009 - 2014)